(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Shout in Crisis
ESSENTIAL PACK
ギラギラに光っちゃって
Shining glittery
Shout in Crisis
SPECIAL ITEMS
ギラギラに光っちゃって
Shining glittery
Attention
"Shout in Crisis" Penlight をお持ちのお客様へ
To customers who have the "Shout in Crisis" Penlight
各楽曲のテイスト・演出に合わせてペンライトのカラーを切り替えて、会場演出のお手伝いをお願いします。
Please help with the venue's production by switching the penlight colors to match each song's taste and staging.
持ち手部分のスイッチで推しカラーの BLUE を固定できます。詳しい使用方法は、ペンライト付属の台紙をご確認ください。
You can fix the BLUE member color with the switch on the handle. For detailed usage instructions, please check the backing card.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the show starts.
Attention 'Shout in Crisis' Penlight をお持ちのお客様へ
Attention: To customers who own the 'Shout in Crisis' Penlight
各楽曲のテイスト・演出に合わせてペンライトのカラーを切り替えて、会場演出のお手伝いをお願いします。
Please help with the venue's production by switching colors to match each song's mood.
持ち手部分のスイッチで推しカラーの BLUE を固定できます。
You can fix the color to 'BLUE' using the switch on the handle.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
オールスターカードゲーム リバース for you!
All-Star Card Game Rebirth for you!
ホロライブの豪華メンバーが
The gorgeous members of Hololive...
カードゲームの舞台に再び！
...return to the card game stage once again!
一緒にきらめきを感じよう！
Let's feel the sparkle together!
ブースターパックプラス ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2
Booster Pack Plus: Hololive Production Vol. 2
2月10日（金）発売！
On sale Friday, February 10th!
ブシロード
Bushiroad
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションが、またまたカードに大集合！
Hololive Production is gathering on cards once again!
広がる、ヴァイスシュヴァルツ。
Expanding, Weiß Schwarz.
ブースターパック『ホロライブプロダクション』Vol.2、3月24日(金)発売！
Booster Pack "Hololive Production" Vol.2, on sale Friday, March 24!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
みるハコ。新しい生活様式で楽しもう！
Miru-hako. Let's enjoy with a new lifestyle!
ライブやフェスに行きたいな～
I want to go to concerts and festivals...
だったら、みるハコ！
In that case, Miru-hako!
大音量のライブ・ビューイングが思いっきり楽しめる！
You can fully enjoy high-volume live viewing!
映画を大きい画面で見たいな～
I want to watch movies on a big screen...
だったら、みるハコ！
In that case, Miru-hako!
大画面のモニターで映画やアニメを楽しもう！
Enjoy movies and anime on a large monitor!
みるハコなら、カラオケボックスで音楽ライブや映画が楽しめる！
With Miru-hako, you can enjoy music concerts and movies in a karaoke room!
ライブ・ビューイングも！
Live viewing, too!
お近くのジョイサウンドで！みるハコ。
At your local Joysound! Miru-hako.
hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP / Geek Jackにてライブグッズ販売中！
Live merchandise now on sale at hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP and Geek Jack!
各楽曲のテイスト・演出に合わせてペンライトのカラーを切り替えて、会場演出のお手伝いをお願いします。
Please help with the venue's production by switching penlight colors to match the style and staging of each song.
Hoshimachi Suisei 2nd Solo Live "Shout in Crisis" 開演までしばらくお待ちください
Hoshimachi Suisei 2nd Solo Live "Shout in Crisis" - The performance will begin shortly
My name is Teddy Powers and I sing with Soul Chance for Gospel.
When you fell on us, you created quite a stir for us girls.
And this song is even much better than...
Shout in Crisis SPECIAL ITEMS
Attention: "Shout in Crisis" Penlight をお持ちのお客様へ
Attention: To customers who have the "Shout in Crisis" penlight.
各楽曲のテイスト・演出に合わせてペンライトのカラーを切り替えて、会場演出のお手伝いをお願いします。
Please help with the venue's production by switching the penlight's color to match each song.
持ち手部分のスイッチで推しカラーの BLUE を固定できます。
You can fix the color to BLUE with the switch on the handle.
公演ハッシュタグ #ぎらぎらほしまち
Performance Hashtag: #GiragiraHoshimachi
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
Shout in Crisis ESSENTIAL PACK
オールスターカードゲーム「Reバース」
All-star card game "Rebirth"
ホロライブの豪華メンバーが、カードゲームの舞台に再び！
The gorgeous members of Hololive return to the card game stage once again!
一緒に煌めきを感じよう！
Let's feel the sparkle together!
ブースターパックプラス ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2
Booster Pack Plus Hololive Production Vol.2
2月10日（金）発売！
On sale Friday, February 10th!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
ブシロード
Bushiroad
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ
Weiss Schwarz
ホロライブプロダクションがまたまたカードに大集合！
Hololive Production is gathering as cards once again!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
The expanding Weiss Schwarz!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2
3月24日(金)発売！
Booster Pack Hololive Production Vol.2
On sale Friday, March 24th!
ブシロード
Bushiroad
みるハコ！ 新しい生活様式で楽しもう！
Miruhako! Let's enjoy with a new lifestyle!
ライブやフェスに行きたいな〜
I want to go to a live concert or festival...
だったらみるハコ！
Then, Miruhako!
大音量のライブビューイングが思いっきり楽しめる！
You can fully enjoy a high-volume live viewing!
映画を大きい画面で見たいな〜
I want to watch movies on a big screen...
だったらみるハコ！
Then, Miruhako!
大画面のモニターで映画やアニメを楽しもう！
Enjoy movies and anime on a large monitor!
みるハコなら、カラオケボックスで
音楽ライブや映画が楽しめる！
With Miruhako, you can enjoy music lives and movies
in a karaoke box!
ライブビューイングも！
Live viewings too!
お近くのジョイサウンドで！
At your local Joysound!
みるハコ
Miruhako
Shout in Crisis SPECIAL ITEMS
Attention "Shout in Crisis" Penlight
Shout in Crisis ESSENTIAL PACK
本日は星街すいせい 2ndソロライブ ”Shout in Crisis”にご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to Hoshimachi Suisei 2nd Solo Live "Shout in Crisis" today.
開演に先立ちまして、お客様にご注意ならびにご案内申し上げます。
Before the performance begins, we have some requests and information for our audience.
本公演は、場内での撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, recording, and the use of video equipment are strictly prohibited inside the venue.
館内は禁煙となっております。
Smoking is prohibited inside the building.
喫煙はご遠慮くださいますようお願い申し上げます。
Please refrain from smoking.
また、本公演は避難誘導等の消灯を行います。
Also, for this performance, the emergency exit lights will be turned off.
万が一避難が必要になった場合は、すぐに非常灯を点灯しますので、係員の指示に従っていただきますようお願いいたします。
In the event that an evacuation becomes necessary, emergency lights will be turned on immediately; please follow the instructions of the staff.
新型コロナウイルス感染拡大防止対策として、マスクの着用、手指の消毒、ソーシャルディスタンスのご協力をお願いしております。
As measures to prevent the spread of COVID-19, we ask for your cooperation in wearing masks, disinfecting hands, and social distancing.
ご観覧いただく際や、ロビー内でもお客様同士の距離間隔を保っていただくよう、ご協力をお願いいたします。
Please cooperate in maintaining distance from other guests while viewing and in the lobby.
入場時に検温にて体調確認させていただいておりますが、
We checked your condition with a temperature check at entry,
万が一体調に異変を感じる場合は、無理をせず係員へお申し出ください。
but if you feel any change in your condition, please do not overdo it and inform the staff.
客席内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ジャンプ等の危険行為、
Dangerous acts such as moshing, diving, and jumping in the audience,
ルールに反したコンサートライトの使用は禁止となります。
and the use of concert lights that violate the rules are prohibited.
以上のことが守られない場合は、コンサートを一時中断、もしくは中止させていただきますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
If the rules are not followed, the concert may be suspended or canceled; thank you for your understanding.
本公演は映像配信、および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席のお客様の様子が映り込む場合がございます。
Broadcasting and photography cameras are in the venue, and members of the audience may be captured on film.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please note that these images and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
コンサート終了後は、危険防止、またディスタンス確保のため、ブロックごとの呼び出しによる規制退場にご協力のほどよろしくお願いいたします。
After the concert, to ensure safety and distance, please cooperate with the staggered exit by block.
係員の指示があるまで、ご自身のお席でお待ちください。
Please wait at your seat until instructed by the staff.
また、昨日政府より表明がありました通り、イベント会場での声出し収容上限が100%となりましたので、
Also, as announced by the government yesterday, the limit for vocal cheering at venues is now 100%,
本公演においても、声を出して応援が可能です。
so vocal cheering is allowed for this performance.
マスク着用の上、節度のある声量でご声援をお送りください。
Please cheer with a moderate volume while wearing a mask.
それでは、まもなく開演いたします。お席についてお待ちください。
The performance will begin shortly. Please wait at your seat.
(Vocalizing)
どこへでも勝手しても大抵平気なつもり
Thinking I'd usually be fine no matter where I acted as I pleased
んなもっと死ぬ気で生きたくもないバックボーンで
With a backbone that doesn't want to live any more desperately than this
染みたいの？ 誇りたいの？ いっそ黙らされたいの？
Do you want to be tainted? Be proud? Or just be silenced?
綺麗な定義もデカいのくれ 私にステージをくれ
Give me beautiful definitions and something big, give me a stage
ねえ全部独り占めにしたい 強欲さ一行って見下ろしたい
I want to keep it all to myself, I want to go to greed and look down
好き勝手やりたい 独尊優雅な体裁で
I want to do as I please, with a self-centered and elegant appearance
たいそうなこと言えてないの定義 決定的に間違ってる
I'm not saying anything grand, the definitions are decisively wrong
あぁ 果てしなき倍に燃やしたいなって
Ah, I want to burn it twice as much endlessly
狭い部屋の中だって鼓動と心臓に
Even in a small room, to the heartbeat and the heart
同調してるんだろう？ あぁ
You're synchronizing, aren't you? Ah
意味深そうに暴走せえ
Run wild as if it's meaningful
心情は問うの？ 鼓動の残響！
Are you asking about feelings? Echo of the heartbeat!
いつかの顔に勝るものなし 知らないならちょっと黙ろうか
Nothing beats a face from back then, if you don't know, shut up for a bit
道を開けろよハニー 世界総括ぶれる
Make way, honey, the world summary is shaking
だだだ漏れたそれだって通して けど正解はずないの
Even that which leaked out, let it through, but it can't be correct
精神を消耗せえ ほら多分捕まえて
Exhaust your spirit, look, maybe catch it
どんな結果だって最高潮！ 救援も飛ばせ
Whatever the result, it's the climax! Send out a rescue call
あぁ もっと死んで勝って独尊で 去る者追わずでいいでしょう
Ah, die and win more and be self-conceit, it's fine not to chase those who leave
縋りたいと言っても見たくて 結局ピルダンスに捕まるだけ
Even if I say I want to cling, I want to see, in the end I'll just be caught in a pill dance
意味深そうに暴走せえ
Run wild as if it's meaningful
心情は問うの？ ちょっと先に待ってて
Are you asking about feelings? Wait a bit ahead
未知 私の全存在を知れ
The unknown, know my whole existence
飽き足らない 見当たらない 誰がカリスマ？
Unsatisfied, nowhere to be found, who's the charisma?
危なすぎる相手は私でしょう？ 見たくて乱れてさ
The one who's too dangerous is me, right? Wanting to see, being disheveled
妄想が全天解できそうじゃん 定型的適圧バグ
The delusion seems like it could fully expand, stereotypical appropriate pressure bug
あぁ 果てしなき倍に燃やしちゃえば
Ah, if I burn it twice as much endlessly
跡形もなくなって歴史になるんだ
It will disappear without a trace and become history
そこに立つ私に あぁ
To me standing there, ah
感情は放つよな火花
Emotions are like sparks being released
それが常識と笑われても知らないんだよ こっちのペースで花は咲き続けるから
Even if it's laughed at as common sense, I don't know, because flowers bloom at my pace
世界総括覆せよ
Overturn the world summary
燃えるほど 尽きるほど ステージは熱くなる
The more it burns, the more it's exhausted, the stage gets hotter
だからまだ振り絞れよハニー
So keep squeezing it out, honey
ちゃんと声は届くから
Because your voice will surely reach
もっと叫びたくなってしまえばいいのになんて思うんだ
I find myself thinking it would be fine if I just felt like screaming more
そこに立つ私に
To me, standing there
あー あー
Ah- ah-
不自由だとかもろもろ順調なんだよ
Things like lack of freedom and everything else are going well
せめてくだらない理由で地を這うような明日じゃないなら
As long as it's not a tomorrow where I'm crawling on the ground for some trivial reason
ちょっと黙ろうか 満ちもいけるよ 悠々
Shall we be quiet for a bit? I can go through the high tide with ease
そこでもっと叫ぶんだ
So I'll scream more there
燃え尽くして
Burn it all out
灼熱に転じて
Turning into a red heat
だって僕は星だから
Because I am a star
きっと君はもう気づいていた
I'm sure you had already noticed
僕の心の奥で書いた
What I wrote deep within my heart
それがこれから話すチープなモノローグさ
That is the cheap monologue I'm about to tell you
ずっと言えない言葉があった
There were words I could never say
凍えそうな風が吹いた
A freezing wind blew
ずっとさ
Forever
ふっと香りだすその匂いか
Is it that scent that suddenly wafts out?
どうしようもなく切なくて
It's so hopelessly heart-wrenching
部屋の隅で膝を抱えて震えていた
I was shivering in the corner of the room, clutching my knees
太陽なんていらないから
Because I don't need something like the sun
明けないでいて
Please don't let the day break
その手を伸ばして
Reach out your hand
誰かに届くように
So that it might reach someone
僕だって君と同じ
Even I'm the same as you
特別なんかじゃない
I'm nothing special
変わらない
I'll never change
そうさ僕は夜を歌え Stella Stellar
That's right, let me sing for the night, Stella Stellar
ありったけの輝きで
With all the radiance I have
今宵僕は ずっとずっと止まない
Tonight, I'll never, ever stop
そうさ僕はずっと泣きたかったのは
That's right, the one who wanted to cry all along
僕シンデレラじゃないさ
I'm not some Cinderella
無口な王子様だって
Even if I'm a silent prince
僕は星空
I'm the starry sky
だって僕は星空
Because I'm the starry sky
なんてありふれた話なんだ
What a cliché story it is
急いで書き連ねていた
I've been hurriedly scribbling it down
ノートの隅に眠る
Sleeping in the corner of my notebook,
ほんの一シーンだ
it's just a single scene
きっとあの星も泣いてるんだ
I'm sure that star is crying too
明日なんて来ないままでいて
Let tomorrow never come
このままいて
Stay just as you are
その手を伸ばして
Reach out that hand
誰かに届くように
So that it reaches someone
本当に大切なものは
It seems the truly important things
目に見えないみたいなんだ
are invisible to the eye
そうさ僕は夜を歌え Stella Stella
That's right, let me sing for the night, Stella Stellar
彩のない輝きで
With a colorless radiance
今宵僕は きっときっと止まない
Tonight, I'm sure, I'm sure I won't stop
そうさ僕はずっと泣きたかったのは
That's right, the one who wanted to cry all along
僕シンデレラじゃないさ
I'm not some Cinderella
救うヒーローは僕だ
I'm the hero who saves the day
You will be the Cinderella
おとぎ話
A fairy tale
そうさ僕は夜を歌え Stella Stella
That's right, let me sing for the night, Stella Stellar
ありったけの輝きで
With all the radiance I have
今宵僕は ずっとずっと止まない
Tonight, I'll never, ever stop
そうさ僕は愛を歌え Stella Stella
That's right, let me sing of love, Stella Stellar
世界中の真ん中で
In the very center of the world
今宵僕は きっときっと止まない
Tonight, I'm sure, I'm sure I won't stop
そうさ僕はずっと泣きたかったのは
That's right, the one who wanted to cry all along
僕シンデレラじゃないさ
I'm not some Cinderella
救うヒーローは僕だ
I'm the hero who saves the day
だって僕は星空
Because I'm the starry sky
Stella Stella
Stella Stellar
みんな！熱くなる準備できてますか！
Everyone! Are you ready to get fired up?!
行くぞ！Shout in Crisis！
Let's go! Shout in Crisis!
画面の向こうの そのまた向こうで
Beyond the screen, and even further beyond,
放たれた言葉たち
the words that were released
殴っても痛まない 楽書き
Graffiti that doesn't hurt even if you hit it
満天の星のように散らばっている
Scattered like a star-filled sky
ガラスの破片の上を
Walking over shards of glass
裸足で歩くような痛みだ
It's a pain like walking barefoot
僕はずっと苦しかったんだ
I've been in pain all this time
そうだ 僕にとって 正解なんてどうだっていい
That's right, to me, the correct answer doesn't matter
この線が確かな誓いだと 自分に決めたなら
If I've decided this line is a certain oath
気付いて 鏡に映った僕もいるわ
I realized even the "me" reflected in the mirror
全部 僕のためにあったのに
was all there for me, but...
気付いたらこの手を離れていた
Before I knew it, it had left my hands
僕の逃げ場の
My place of refuge
輪郭さえぼやけそうな夜も
In nights where even the outlines seem to blur
僕の全部取り返さなくちゃ
I have to take back everything of mine
何度剥ぎ取ったって
No matter how many times it's torn away
煩いくらいになるのいつか
It'll become loud enough to be annoying someday
突き放そうとしたって
Even if I tried to push it away
泥臭いのにしがみついて
I'd cling to it, even if it's unsightly
もう僕は売らない
I won't sell myself out anymore
この街の事情
To the circumstances of this city
リソースは全部自分を
All my resources, for myself
大きくはしない
I won't make them bigger
僕のこの罪も
This sin of mine
姿、形も
My appearance and form
誰に決められることもなく
Without anyone deciding them for me
そっと僕にとって
Softly, to me
世界なんてどうだっていい
The world doesn't matter at all
この全部が確か
All of this is certainly
間違いだって自分で決めるから
Even if it's a mistake, because I'll decide it for myself
あの愛おしさの
That precious
輝きにも
Brightness too
僕が蔓延る
I will spread out
虚勢にも
And in my bluffing
届かなくたって構わない
I don't care if I don't reach
僕以外何もいらない！
I don't need anything but myself!
Finally, it's started.
I think with 20 costumes for tonight...
When you fell out of space...
Final songs for us together.
And this song is for everyone...
Called The Debut of the Year 2018.
Just for show, just for show...
ゼロとイチで
With zeros and ones
完成した目に合わす
Matching eyes that have been completed
誰にも見せないままで
While showing no one
Just for show, just for show...
鮮明なほどギャップ濁らせて
Making the gap cloudier the clearer it gets
歌い出すわ
I'll start singing
In case I don't see you
ために目に焼き付けてあげる
I'll burn it into my eyes for you
Loose
不相応でいけるわ
I can go even if it's ill-suited
無邪気なほど解像度急行
Resolution rushing like innocence
消失するものされるもの
Things that vanish, things that are vanished
美しく全部壊しちゃえ
Break it all beautifully
腹括ってぶち込め
Steeling myself and plunging in
Ten, one, start!
気触れてる不感症にも
To those tainted by insensitivity
笑ってあげる
I'll laugh for you
強がりじゃないよだってあなたとほら
It's not a bluff, because look, with you
トゥルルル...
Turururu...
強制リロード待って間違った
Wait, forced reload, I made a mistake
嘘じゃない
It's not a lie
あれもこれも全部愛と言い放とう
Let's declare that everything is love
彗星のごとく現れたスターの原石
A star in the making, appearing like a comet
アイドルVTuberの星街すいせいでーす！
Idol VTuber, Hoshimachi Suisei here!
すいちゃんはー！
Sui-chan is!
今日も可愛い！
Cute again today!
革命の準備終わらせすぎ
Over-prepared for the revolution
乗り込める希望はラージサイズ級
The hope I can board is large-sized
シュビドゥビドゥビドゥバ
Shubidubidubiduba
お前ら叫べタッチアンドゴー！
You guys shout, touch and go!
ゼロとイチの間に
Between zeros and ones
白く吐き出した
Breathed out in white
In case I don't see you
ありゃりゃなんだこれこれどっか見た風景
Ara-ra, what's this? A landscape I've seen somewhere
またお色直しが美しく絶好調
Another costume change, beautiful and in peak condition
こんな場所で終わらせない準備はよう
Ready not to let it end in a place like this
君も君も
You too, and you too
濁ってる不感症も抱きしめてあげる
I'll embrace even the clouded insensitivity
無知じゃないのだってあなたとほら
I'm not ignorant, because look, with you
トゥルルル...
Turururu...
言葉が咲き出すただ欲しいと歌う
Words begin to bloom, singing just that I want it
偶像じゃない
Not an idol [statue]
人混みの中で全部愛と言い放とう
Let's declare that everything is love in the crowd
喰らう、何万回と蘇生
Chow down, revived tens of thousands of times
行けば救世
If I go, it's salvation
挑むべき場所、意義、意味
The place to challenge, significance, meaning
ゾーン、ゾーン、皆探してる
Zone, zone, everyone's searching
手のひらに答えがなくば
If the answer isn't in the palm of your hand
Vもリアルも関係ない
V or real doesn't matter
旅立て空の向こうに！
Set out to the other side of the sky!
いびつな 不分丈 今も笑ってあげる
I'll give you a smile even now, in these misshapen shorts
嘘じゃないよ だってあなたもほら
It's not a lie, because look, you are too
小細工で理論だっても また間違えた
Even with tricks and theories, I made another mistake
嘘じゃない
It's not a lie
いびつな 不分丈 抱きしめてあげる
I'll give you a hug, in these misshapen shorts
無知じゃないの だってあなたもほら
I'm not ignorant, because look, you are too
不器用だ 先立っても ただ欲しいと歌う
Even if I'm clumsy and ahead of myself, I sing because I just want it
嘘じゃない
It's not a lie
受け止めて おいちゃうでしょ
You'll accept it, won't you?
おいちゃうでしょ
Won't you?
えー、星街すいせい2ndソロライブ「Shout in Crisis」にご来場ありがとうございます！
Welcome to Hoshimachi Suisei's 2nd solo live, "Shout in Crisis"!
ほー、やばい。ここで飛び跳ねると後半の体力がなくなっちゃうので...
Whoa, boy. If I keep jumping like this, I'll run out of energy for the second half...
...落ち着きますけど、皆さん！
...so I'll calm down, but everyone!
なんと今日は、声が出せるんですよね！
Believe it or not, cheering is allowed today!
うわ、久しぶりすぎるこの感覚。もうね、今日も可愛いって言ってもらえて、
Wow, it's been so long since I've felt this. Having you all call me "cute" again...
めっちゃ気持ちよかったです。ありがとうございます。
...felt amazing. Thank you so much.
いや、もうファーストに比べて、もうセカンドはとんでもなくデカい会場になりまして。
Man, compared to the first one, this second live is in a ridiculously huge venue.
えー、5階まであるそうです。
I heard it goes all the way up to the 5th floor.
5階の皆さん！
Everyone on the 5th floor!
4階の皆さん、3階の皆さん、2階の皆さん、アリーナ！
4th floor, 3rd floor, 2nd floor, and the Arena!
はい、えーつい先日発売したニューアルバム「Specter」はみんな聴いてくれましたか？
So, did everyone listen to my new album "Specter" that just came out the other day?
なんと今回は、素敵なバンドメンバーの皆さんと、その曲たちを披露したいと思います！
For this live, I'll be performing those songs with an amazing group of band members!
はい、えー配信で見てるみんなのコメントも見えてます。
Yes, I can also see the comments from everyone watching the stream.
ここ、ここがね、なんか配信用のカメラらしくて、おーい！イエーイ！
This camera right here is for the stream, apparently. Hello! Yeah!
会場のみんなも多分見えてる. 見えてるよね？わーい！
You guys in the venue can probably see it too, right? Yay!
イエーイ！生バンドすげぇっていうコメントもなんとなく、宙に浮いてるコメント読めるんだけど。
Yeah! I can even read the floating comments saying things like "The live band is awesome!"
パチパチありがとう。
Thanks for the applause.
はい、すいちゃんと目が合えるこのカメラ、あの度々抜いてもらえますんで、これ是非ね、注目してください。
This camera that lets you make eye contact with Sui-chan will be used often, so please look forward to it.
あ、そうだ、いつもの挨拶ね。なんか曲中でしかやってなかったから。
Oh, right! My usual greeting. I've only done it during songs so far.
やったほうがいいですよね！
I should do it properly, shouldn't I?
そいじゃ、行きますよ！
All right, here we go!
彗星の如く現れたスターの原石！アイドルVTuberの星街すいせいです！
A diamond in the rough who descended like a comet! I'm idol VTuber Hoshimachi Suisei!
すいちゃんはー？
Sui-chan is...?
今日も可愛いー！
...cute today, too!
最高！声出し最高！嬉しい！
The best! Cheering is the best! I'm so happy!
うわ、もう無理だと思いましたよ、声を出すのは。
Man, I really thought it wouldn't be possible to have cheering.
なんと、もう今日になって、あの会場に着いてから運営さんに...
But actually, just today, after I arrived at the venue, the staff told me...
「すいせいさん、ビッグニュースがあります。声出しOKです」って言われて。
"Suisei-san, we have big news. Cheering is allowed."
やったー！いや嬉しい、みんなもね、存分に声出してください。
We did it! I'm so glad. Everyone, please cheer to your heart's content.
お隣さんにね、気を使ってね、楽しんでくださいね。
Just be mindful of the people next to you and have a great time.
えー、ハッシュタグ「ぎらぎら星街」で今日のライブはツイートしてほしいです。
I'd love for you to tweet about today's live using the hashtag #ぎらぎら星街.
あの配信の皆さんとかね、お願いします。トレンドに入ってるんじゃないかな？今、何位？
Especially those of you watching the stream. Is it trending yet? What's the rank?
お、なんかライブ始まる前に1位になって... ありがとうございます！
Oh, it hit number one before the live even started! Thank you so much!
あー嬉しい。わーい！
I'm so happy. Yay!
はい、えーではでは、えーYouTubeとTikTokで見てるみんなはここでお別れになってしまうので...
All right then, it's time to say goodbye to everyone watching on YouTube and TikTok...
...ぜひぜひ、配信チケットを買って続きをご覧ください。
...so please, buy a streaming ticket and watch the rest!
君たち見れるでしょ？君たちは見れるでしょ！
You guys can watch it, right? You definitely can!
はい、なんか今回は、初めて、あのTikTokでチラ見せ...
Yeah, this is actually the first time we've done a "sneak peek" on TikTok...
配信もやってるらしくてね。
I heard they're also doing a stream.
もうこれはZ世代の、あの…
This is definitely something that...
男女にめちゃめちゃ注目されるんじゃないか？
...Z Generation boys and girls will pay a lot of attention to, right?
バズりたい！バズりたいすいちゃん！
I want to go viral! Suisei who wants to go viral!
TikTokでバズりたい！
I want to go viral on TikTok!
はい。じゃあ買ってくださいね！
Yes. So please buy it!
はい。では、今日は…
Alright. Well, today...
いつものアイドルVTuber星街すいせいとは…
Differing from the usual idol VTuber Hoshimachi Suisei...
ちょっと一味違う、私をお見せできればと思います。
...I hope to show you a slightly different side of myself.
会場のみんなも、配信のみんなも、
Everyone at the venue, everyone on the stream,
まだまだ盛り上がる準備できてますかー！？
Are you ready to get even more hyped!?
それでは聴いてください。
Now, please listen.
灼熱にて純情！
Syakunetsu nite Junjou!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free part has ended
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free part has ended
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!